export const data = [
    {
        question: "Which sense do cats not taste?",
        option1: "Sour",
        option2: "Sweetness",
        option3: "Bitterness",
        option4: "Saltiness",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What does it mean when a cat sticks its butt in your face?",
        option1: "They are angry",
        option2: "They want food",
        option3: "It's a gesture of friendship",
        option4: "They want to play",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Cats are nearsighted, but their night vision is:",
        option1: "Worse than humans",
        option2: "Nonexistent",
        option3: "The same as humans",
        option4: "Better than humans",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Which bone in a cat's body is unique compared to humans?",
        option1: "Collarbone",
        option2: "Femur",
        option3: "Spine",
        option4: "Skull",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "When a cat flops over and exposes his belly, it means:",
        option1: "He wants a belly rub",
        option2: "He is scared",
        option3: "He is angry",
        option4: "He is relaxed and showing trust",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "If your cat approaches you with a straight, almost vibrating tail, it means:",
        option1: "She is scared",
        option2: "She is annoyed",
        option3: "She is extremely happy to see you",
        option4: "She wants to play",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "A cat with a question-mark-shaped tail is:",
        option1: "Asking, 'Want to play?'",
        option2: "Feeling scared",
        option3: "Annoyed",
        option4: "Hungry",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "How many different vocalizations can cats have?",
        option1: "Up to 10",
        option2: "Up to 50",
        option3: "Up to 100",
        option4: "Up to 200",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Who do cats develop meowing behavior for?",
        option1: "Other cats",
        option2: "Birds",
        option3: "Dogs",
        option4: "People",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Which paw do male cats predominantly use?",
        option1: "Right paw",
        option2: "Left paw",
        option3: "Both paws equally",
        option4: "None of the above",
        ans: 2,
    },
];